ABOUT

A Gadjah Mada University graduate with more than three years of progressive experience in architecture and planning. I have developed a comprehensive understanding of practical insight into planning and design and developed my skill in any software. As a dedicated, hardworking, and proactive person, I am always excited to learn something new, and handling multiple tasks at one period of time would not be an issue at all. More than that, I loved the challenge, and motivate me to be a person who not makes problems as a barrier but create the problems as opportunities.

EDUCATION

- Gadjah Mada University / 2013 - 2017 / Bachelor of Engineering in Architecture

Coursework: Sustainable Architecture (Final Project), Thematic Design Studio, Architectural Criticism, Architecture Theory, Professional Practice in Architecture, Ecological Human Settlement, Introduction for Housing Development, Architecture Design for Hospital, Tropical Building Design, Professional Ethics and Building Codes, etc.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

- PT Pembangunan Jaya Ancol, Tbk. / Dec, 2017 - present.

Architect

Working on the daily project and a strategic project in the recreation area taught me how to be a creative designer and manage the project in a tight time and budget. Responsible for delivering the projects from the idea/storyline until supervising the construction, my roles are but not limited to:

- Generated the ideas for the new development
- Designing for the innovation and renovation projects
- Responsible for coordinating and organizing the projects with the in-house team, procurement team, construction team, and external certified experts.
- Responsible for preparing the material of the presentation.
- Responsible for supervising the progress of construction.
- Monitoring all progress of projects periodically & reporting to the manager and up.
- PT Global Rancang Selaras / Oct, 2016 Nov, 2017

Assistant Architect

Assisted architects in all aspects and responsible for preparing material for presentation, creating reports, surveying sites, etc.

- Directorate Planning and Development UGM / Feb, 2016 - May, 2016 Personal Assistant

Helped to collect the data and make the presentation (report) on several projects such as Code Dewobronto Tourism Village and Kuningan UGM area.

SOCIAL EXPERIENCE

- Community Service

As one of the foremost and the outermost islands in Indonesia, Marampit Island is located between Indonesia and the Philippines. To support them, we brought the program titled "Increasing the Economies Value of Fish and Coconut and Marampit Island's Quality of Human Resources to Support Maritim Strengthening in Marampit Island as an Overseas Homepage in Marampit Village, Nanusa District, Talaud Island Regency, North Sulawesi Province, Indonesia".

SKILLS

Sketch 8/10 CorelDraw 8/10 PhotoShop 8/10 AutoCad 8/10 Sketchup 8/10 Lumion 9/10 3DsMax 4/10 Archicad 4/10

Email: 4smaul@gmail.com

linkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/asmaulh

Ig: @asmaulh___

"Life isn't about finding yourself. Life is about creating yourself."

- George Bernard Shaw

"Don't wait for the right opportunity: create it."

- George Bernard Shaw

Let's collaborate!

Projects:

- 1. EDUCATION FOR SUSTAINABLE DEVELOPMENT CENTER / Academic Project / Conceptual Design
- 2. CULTURAL CENTER / Academic Project / Conceptual Design
- 3. NLINGGOTEA RESORT & SPA / Academic Project / Conceptual Design
- 4. CITY HOTEL / Academic Project / Conceptual Design
- 5. JOGJA MOVEMENT HUB / Academic Project / Conceptual Design / Team Work
- 6. THE SEASIDE RESORT / Professional Project / Conceptual Design
- 7. W HOUSE / Professional Project / Constructed
- 8. MBA OFFICE / Professional Project / Conceptual Design
- 9. INDUSTRIAL CAFE/ Professional Project / Conceptual Design
- 10. FOLK SCHOOL / Professional Project / Constructed
- 11. CITYWALK/ Professional Project / Process to Construction
- 12. ENTRANCE OF ANCOL ART MARKET/ Professional Project / Conceptual Design
- 13. THEME PARK / Professional Project / Constructed
- 14. ASSISTANT ARCHITECT PROJECT
- 15. OTHERS



THANK YOU WAHYUUUUU!



Salam dari kekeyi kesukaan adit.